[{"answer": " I am so glad tomorrow is Friday.  Its been an exhausting week", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " I know.  Its been pretty hectic.  I cant wait until I can stop working and stay a", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 14, "question": " I am so glad tomorrow is Friday.  Its been an exhausting week", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Hopefully, Ill get that promotion soon and then you can quit your job.    My bos", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 18, "question": " I know.  Its been pretty hectic.  I cant wait until I can stop working and stay a", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Well see.  If all goes well, maybe I can quit in a few months", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Hopefully, Ill get that promotion soon and then you can quit your job.    My bos", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": "So, what have we got planned for the weekend?  Anything exciting", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Well see.  If all goes well, maybe I can quit in a few months", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Well, remember that tomorrow night Amy and Chris are coming over for dinne", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 24, "question": "So, what have we got planned for the weekend?  Anything exciting", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I almost forgot.  At what time", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Well, remember that tomorrow night Amy and Chris are coming over for dinne", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Seven oclock", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I almost forgot.  At what time", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " I guess we should expect them around 8:00 then, eh", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Seven oclock", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " They are always late.  Ha ha", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 34, "question": " I guess we should expect them around 8:00 then, eh", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " So, what are you making", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 35, "question": " They are always late.  Ha ha", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " I thought Id make salad and lasagna and then chocolate cake for dessert", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 36, "question": " So, what are you making", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Yum.  Chocolate cake sounds good", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 37, "question": " I thought Id make salad and lasagna and then chocolate cake for dessert", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " That reminds me.  Weve got to go to the store tomorrow to pick up som", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Yum.  Chocolate cake sounds good", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " No  Not the one where you have to sing and pretend to be different famou", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 42, "question": " That reminds me.  Weve got to go to the store tomorrow to pick up som", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Yes, that one.  Come on, Doug.  It will be fun", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 46, "question": " No  Not the one where you have to sing and pretend to be different famou", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Fine, fine.  Ill try it.  What about Saturday?  Whats going on then", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Yes, that one.  Come on, Doug.  It will be fun", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Well, Saturday afternoon Im going to a baby shower for Pauline at work", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Fine, fine.  Ill try it.  What about Saturday?  Whats going on then", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " I didnt know she was pregnant", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Well, Saturday afternoon Im going to a baby shower for Pauline at work", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Yep, she is.  The boys have a soccer game at 12:00, so youll have to tak", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 50, "question": " I didnt know she was pregnant", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " What?  I was going to watch the football game at 12:30 with the guys", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Yep, she is.  The boys have a soccer game at 12:00, so youll have to tak", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Sorry, Doug.  What do you want me to do?  I have to go to the shower, so ", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 55, "question": " What?  I was going to watch the football game at 12:30 with the guys", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " No.  Ill take them.  I guess I can record the game", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Sorry, Doug.  What do you want me to do?  I have to go to the shower, so ", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Good.  Saturday night I told the boys wed have family night", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 60, "question": " No.  Ill take them.  I guess I can record the game", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " What are we going to do", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Good.  Saturday night I told the boys wed have family night", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " I thought we could maybe take them out for pizza and then a movie.  What d", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 62, "question": " What are we going to do", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " That sounds good.  What movie", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 66, "question": " I thought we could maybe take them out for pizza and then a movie.  What d", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " I dont know.  Is there anything theyve said they want to see", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 67, "question": " That sounds good.  What movie", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " I think they wanted to see that new one with Pamela Anderson", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 68, "question": " I dont know.  Is there anything theyve said they want to see", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Doug.  We need a movie for the kids, not you", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 72, "question": " I think they wanted to see that new one with Pamela Anderson", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Im just kidding.  How about that new Disney movie", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Doug.  We need a movie for the kids, not you", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Yeah, thatd be good.  Can you check the paper to see what time its playing", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Im just kidding.  How about that new Disney movie", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Sure, Ill do that", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Yeah, thatd be good.  Can you check the paper to see what time its playing", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Thanks, baby.  I guess that just leaves Sunday.  Do we have any plans fo", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Sure, Ill do that", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " I hope not", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Thanks, baby.  I guess that just leaves Sunday.  Do we have any plans fo", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " I dont think we do.  Lets just relax that day", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 81, "question": " I hope not", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Sounds good to me", "docId": "11-04", "aSentId": 82, "question": " I dont think we do.  Lets just relax that day", "qSentId": 81}]
